<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" 
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">

<channel>
      <title>Publications-rsses in Yukio Fukuzawa </title>
	  <itunes:subtitle>Yukio Fukuzawa's personal blogs</itunes:subtitle>
	  <itunes:author>Yukio Fukuzawa</itunes:author>
	  <itunes:owner>
	  <itunes:name>Yukio Fukuzawa</itunes:name>
	  <itunes:email>y@ this domain</itunes:email>
	  </itunes:owner>
	  <itunes:category text="Education">
	  <itunes:category text="Higher Education"/>
	  </itunes:category>
	  <itunes:keywords>phd, latex, yukio fukuzawa, massey, new zealand</itunes:keywords>
	  <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
	  <itunes:image href="http://www.ukio.info//img/avatar2.jpg" />
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://www.ukio.info/publications/index.xml</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
 
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation of Harmonic Syllables in Noisy Recordings of Bird Vocalisations</title>
      <link>http://www.ukio.info/publications/ivcnz2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ukio.info/publications/ivcnz2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The  study  of  birdsong  has  implications  in  a  num-ber  of  biological  and  conservational  applications.  However,  theanalysis of bird vocalisations in the natural habitat is still largelya  laborious  task.  One  of  the  bottle  necks  is  the  segmentation  ofbird  vocalisations  into  individual  syllables.  Simple  segmentationin  time  domain  proves  difficult  because  of  overlapping  signalsover  different  frequency  bands.  The  common  approach  is  toconvert  audio  recordings  into  a  spectrogram  and  apply  imageprocessing  techniques  to  pick  out  the  signal  of  interest.  Weexamine several methods that have been proposed recently to dojust this and find that they are inadequate to deal with harmonicvocalisations.  We  propose  a  method  that  segments  syllables  bylooking  for  the  fundamental  frequency  first  then  works  its  wayup in the frequency axis to find other harmonics if they exist. Weevaluate  our  method  against  another  popular  method  and  findthat the proposed method can segment correctly more than 70%the number of syllables, more than twice that of the method weare  comparing  to&lt;/p&gt;
]]></description>
    </item>
    
 
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Sign Recognition system on Android devices</title>
      <link>http://www.ukio.info/publications/thesis2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ukio.info/publications/thesis2013/</guid>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;This project implements on an Android device a Traﬃc Sign Recognition(TSR) system capable of recognising 85 New Zealand traﬃc signs with variouscolours and shapes. I ﬁnd it possible to have such system running almost realtime on medium-class Android devices by having the core processing modulewritten in native code, interacting with the user interface via JNI calls. Dif-ferent techniques are used to extract sign candidates from raw images beforethey are classiﬁed to the correct class. The ﬁrst technique uses a colour ﬁlteroperating on either HSV or RGB colour space to ﬁlter out non-sign pixelsand the sign detector is applied on the remaining part of the images. Thesecond technique applies the detector on two consecutive raw images withoutcolour-ﬁltering. Sign detector is a AdaBoost classiﬁer using Linear BinaryPattern (LBP) to extract features. Products of sign detector are called ”signcandidates” and recognised by a back propagating neural network. This reportﬁnds the colour-ﬁltering technique with the ﬁltering threshold carefully tunedoverperforms the cascade detecting technique, but the latter is less likely tomiss a sign in diﬀerent lighting conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
]]></description>
    </item>
    
 
    <item>
      <title>q-State Potts model -Theory and simulation</title>
      <link>http://www.ukio.info/publications/q-state-potts-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.ukio.info/publications/q-state-potts-model/</guid>
      <description>&lt;![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;This paper reports a studies into ferromagnetic (or likelihood preferential) Potts model, its statistical mechanics meaning, and propose a simulation tool to simulate the models with given sizes and number of states (q) using Monte-Carlo method. Simulation performance is also discussed.&lt;/p&gt;
]]></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>